Liam Neufeld

Marketing and Sales Assistant

@liam.neufeld@sasktel.net (306) 716-8679 Saskatoon, SK

Inlinkedin.com/in/liam-neufeld Qqithub.com/LNeuf ✓ behance.net/LNeuf ··· Personal Website

Recent University of Saskatchewan graduate with a bachelor's in interactive design. Driven, creative, and dedicated professional individual with superb problem-solving and decision-making abilities. Excited to start career, sharpen skills, and gain experience.

Education

Bachelor of Arts and Science in Interactive Systems Design

University of Saskatchewan

09/2017 - 06/2023 Minor: Psychology Certificate: Computing

Work Experience

Marketing and Sales Assistant

Braid Flooring & Window Fashions

09/2023 - Present

- Plan, coordinate, and execute marketing and projects.
- Process product reception and delivery
- Assist customers with window fashions products and services.
- Assist with window fashion data entry and unloading.

Service Team Member / Technical Advisor

Saskatoon Soccer Centre Inc.

10/2021 - 03/2023

- Interact with guests in a friendly manner and maintained Centres and fields for guest activities.
- Supervised centres independently.
- Trained new employees.
- Set up and maintained facilities' scheduling program and website, which guests use to find games.
- Former Henk Ruys Centre Captain.

Line Cook

Brown's Social House (Lawson Heights)

05/2021 - 08/2021

Line Cook / Delivery Driver

Haywood's Grill

05/2017 - 02/2021

Volunteer Experience

Volunteer Lead - Game Development Workshop

Digitized

05/2023

- Guided students to workshops around campus.
- Assisted workshop leader with Unity course setup on lab computers.
- Helped answer and direct questions from dozens of students during workshop.

Projects

Android Studio Geocache App

- Worked alongside a team of 4 other students to design and implement a geocache database app.
- Utilized Android Studio and Google Maps API to create app.
- Acted as Scrum Lead and Head UI Programmer.

Tyranny of the Feline

- Worked alongside a team of 10 other students to create a small boss-fight arena game.
- Practiced Agile development methodologies.
- Utilized Unity and Aseprite to create game assets.
- Acted as lead character and UI artist